The principles of a devil summoning.
악마 소환 법칙
A devil summoned by sorcery
마법으로 소환된 악마는
must be sent back by sorcery.
마법으로만 귀환한다
The human summoner becomes the devil's master.
인간 소환자는 그 악마의 주인이 된다
As long as the summoner lives,
그 소환자가 살아있는 한
the devil is bound to the human world.
그 악마는 인간 세계를 떠날 수 없다
-Got a package for ya! -Thank you.
- 택배 왔습니다! - 고맙습니다
-I-It was just a dream. -Please sign here.
- 그, 그냥 꿈이야 - 여기 서명하세요
-A dream? No, more like... -Thanks, have a great day!
- 꿈? 아니, 꼭... - 고맙습니다, 안녕히 가세요
-It's wrong to lie. -You too.
- 거짓말은 나쁜 거야 - 안녕히 계세요
Won’t leave
떠나려면
without a dropkick on her!
저 애에게 드롭킥을 날려야 해
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas
자자스 자자스 나사타나다 자자스
-She summoned me, the evil god. -Evil god!
- 저 애가 소환한 난 악마다 - 악마다!
I gotta kill her or else What?
저 애를 죽이지 않으면 뭐?
I can’t go back to Hell! Sister...
지옥에 갈 수가 없어 자매여...
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Life next to death, I combat with my chainsaw!
그래! 그래! 그래! 죽음과 살기 위해, 전기톱으로 싸워야지!
If you go too far,
네가 막 나가면
I’ll slice you up completely!
널 완전히 썰어버릴 거야!
Your halo! Must get it back!
네 후광을 반드시 되찾아야지!
Never miss a chance Hey, seriously?
기회를 절대 놓치지 마 정말 그럴 거야?
To attack her from behind! You’re so mean.
뒤에서 공격하려고? 넌 못됐어
I’ll never give up.
난 절대 포기 안 해
Yurine, you’re off your guard!
유리네, 방심하고 있군!
Now! Time to finish you with the Royal Copenhagen!
지금이다! 로열코펜하겐으로 끝내주지!
Huh? What? I missed…
어, 뭐지? 실패다...
Can’t leave Earth
지구를 떠나려면
without a dropkick on her!
저 애에게 드롭킥을 날려야 해
But until then,
하지만 그때까진
let’s all have fun together! Yeah!
모두 같이 놀자! 신난다!
Tokyo, the big city.
대도시 도쿄
In the corner of this world,
이 세계의 한 외딴곳에서
another day of bittersweet drama
어느 날 달곰씁쓸한 일이
is about to unfold.
벌어진다
Let the hot pot party begin!
스키야키 파티를 시작한다!
You're all in for a treat! It's grade A beef!
내가 모두에게 한턱낼게! 최고급 쇠고기야!
It's not like you bought it.
네가 산 게 아니잖아
D-Don't sweat the details.
작은 일에 신경 쓰지 마
Let's get started!
이제 시작하자!
After heating up the pot, we grease it with beef tallow.
냄비를 가열하고 소기름을 바르지
Then, we'll grill the green onions!
그리고 대파를 굽는 거야
Work up that appetite!
식욕이 돋네
Smells delicious!
맛있는 냄새가 나!
It smells wonderful!
냄새가 정말 좋다!
We'll take them out once they brown so we can grill the meat.
갈색이 되면 꺼내고 고기를 굽는 거지
Please, God, forgive me.
신이시여, 절 용서하소서
Forgive me for attending a witch's Sabbath when I'm an angel.
천사인 제가 악마의 연회에 참석한 걸 용서하소서
Yurine Hanazono, you kidnapped me when I was starving.
하나조노 유리네 넌 굶고 있는 나를 납치했다
What are you scheming?
네 속셈이 뭐지?
No matter how hungry I am,
내가 아무리 배가 고파도
I can't face God after this!
연회가 끝난 후 난 신을 마주할 수 없다
Make sure both sides are cooked.
양쪽이 다 익었는지 확인하고
Meat, meat, I love meat!
고기, 고기다 내가 사랑하는 고기!
Once it's fully cooked, it's time for...
고기가 다 익으면 이젠
Jashin-chan's special stock!
사신짱의 특별 육수를 넣는 거지!
We'll pour this right in!
바로 다 쏟아부을 거야
U-Unbelievable.
기, 기막히다
Today's stock is especially divine!
오늘 육수는 특별히 더 좋군!
I must be a genius!
난 천재야!
Now we put in the veggies,
이제 채소를 넣는 거지
cook them until brown, and it's done!
갈색이 될 때까지 끓이면 다 된 거지!
-I'm jealous, Yurine. -Let me help you.
- 부럽다, 유리네 - 내가 도와줄게
You have generous relatives who send you quality meat.
넌 이런 좋은 고기를 보내주는 맘 좋은 친척이 있잖아
It's not a regular thing.
늘 있는 일이 아니야
That's right!
맞아!
-We rarely have meat in hot pots. -Huh?
- 우리는 스키야키에 고기를 자주 안 넣어 - 응?
It's usually full of veggies.
평소엔 채소만 가득하지
NO MEAT
'고기 없음'
Guess I was lucky today.
오늘은 운 좋은 날이야
Why don't you get your relatives to send us some meat in return?
대신 너희 친척에게 고기 좀 보내라고 하면 어때?
Because that'll make us cannibals.
그러면 우리는 식인종이 되는 거야
Ah, the hot pot's almost ready.
요리가 거의 다 됐다
Looks delicious.
맛있겠다
Here, Pekola, here's your egg.
받아, 페코라 네 달걀이야
-Thanks. -Now dig in!
- 고마워 - 이제 먹어!
Let's eat!
먹자!
I've no choice.
어쩔 수 없지
I'm starving.
난 굶었어
-God will forgive me. -Delicious!
- 신이 용서하실 거야 - 맛있다!
It just melts in my mouth!
입에서 그냥 녹는다!
It's all right.
괜찮네
Pekola! What are you doing here?
페코라! 너 여기서 뭐 하는 거야?
This is a devil's dinner.
이건 악마의 저녁이다
Coming from Heaven,
넌 천국에서 왔으니
you're forbidden to eat with us, aren't you?
우리랑 같이 먹으면 안 되는 거잖아?
Wait, Pekola's an angel?
잠깐, 페코라가 천사야?
-Seriously? -But you invited me.
- 정말? - 하지만 네가 초대했잖아
-Hey! Come by tonight for hot pot! -Hot pot?
- 오늘 밤에 스키야키 먹으러 와! - 스키야키?
Jashin-chan...
사신짱...
You fool.
넌 바보야
W-Who are you calling a fool?
누, 누구더러 바보라는 거야?
She's the one who lost her halo and can't go back to Heaven!
후광을 잃어버려서 천국에 못 가는 건 쟤라고!
T-That's...
그, 그건...
Enough already.
그만해라
Shut up! Not another word!
시끄러워! 한마디도 더 하지 마!
-Jashin-chan... -What?
- 사신짱... - 뭐?
-Let's just enjoy our meal. -But!
- 밥이나 맛있게 먹자 - 하지만!
Do not ruin this meal.
식사를 망치지 마
-Got it? -Yes, ma'am.
- 알겠어? - 네, 마님
Just kidding! Forget everything. Let's enjoy our meal.
농담이야! 다 잊고 맛있게 먹자
W-What's wrong with you?
너, 왜 이러는 거야?
Here! Let me make your plate for you!
있어 봐! 내가 음식을 덜어 줄게!
-We're best friends! -Jashin-chan...
- 우린 제일 친한 친구야 - 사신짱...
Such a handful.
정말 다루기 힘들군
Here ya go, fallen angel.
자, 먹어라 타락한 천사
VEGGIES
'채소'
Not one slice of meat...
고기가 한 점도 없어...
Can't go wrong with Wagyu beef, right?
와규 쇠고기는 언제나 맛있지 않니?
May I get some meat too?
나도 고기를 먹어도 돼?
Rule number one.
규칙 1
Finish everything in your bowl before you go for seconds.
네 그릇에 있는 걸 다 먹어야 음식을 더 가져갈 수 있다
My house, my rules.
내 집에선 내 규칙을 따라
Oh, it's out of this world!
정말 너무 맛있다!
So tender and juicy...
부드럽고 육즙이...
And I'm an angel, not a fallen angel...
난 천사지 타락한 천사가 아니야
-Delicious! -The veggies are good, but...
- 맛나다! - 채소도 좋지만...
-Scrumptious! -They're good, but...
- 끝내주게 맛있다! - 이것도 맛있지만...
The meat...
고기는...
Cow...horse...
소... 말...
Finally...
드디어...
Bok choy sure does fill you up.
청경채를 먹으니 배가 부르네
-It's time-- -You finished, Pekola!
- 이번엔... - 너 다 먹었구나, 페코라!
Let me get that for you!
내가 덜어줄게
Here ya go, fallen angel.
자, 먹어라 타락한 천사
Bon appétit.
많이 먹어
Jashin-chan, cut the bullying!
사신짱, 그만 괴롭혀
You're such a child.
넌 정말 유치해
See what I mean?
내 말이 그 말이야
Here, Pekola, say, "Ah."
자, 페코라 "아" 해 봐
How is it?
어때?
Delicious.
맛있어
I'm so glad.
잘됐다
A-An angel.
처, 천사다
So who exactly is the angel here?
대체 누가 천사지?
Here, Pekola, have some more meat.
받아, 페코라 고기 좀 더 먹어
Don't worry about the rules.
규칙 같은 건 걱정하지 마
There.
됐다
Damn it! You're all spoiling her rotten!
젠장! 모두가 저 애를 버릇 나쁘게 만드는군!
Medusa, Minos, you're both devils! Why are you taking the angel's side?
메두사, 미노스, 너희는 악마야 왜 천사의 편을 드는 거야?
Ignore her.
쟤는 무시해
Y-Yurine...
유, 유리네...
If you're gonna play it like that...
네가 이렇게 나온다면
I'll just have to eat all the meat!
고기를 내가 다 먹는 수밖에!
-The meat... -Hey...
- 고기가... - 야...
Don't do it...
하지 마
All done!
다 먹었다!
J-J-Jashin-chan!
사, 사신짱!
-The meat... -How could you?
- 고기... - 너 어떻게 이럴 수가?
It used to be
이 냄비엔
a hot pot full of meat.
고기가 한가득 있었다
Our lovely meal...
우리 사랑스러운 음식을...
Jashin-chan...
사신짱
How will you pay for this?
어떻게 대가를 치를 거지?
You won't get away with this.
그냥 넘어갈 순 없어
What? You wanna try me? Huh?
뭐? 해보자는 거야? 어?
I-I'll go buy more meat!
내가 가서 고기를 더 사 올게!
There's not enough meat, you see?
고기가 충분치 않잖아 너도 알지?
I'll end you first!
내가 널 먼저 끝내주지!
I'm stuck here thanks to you. All that resentment
네가 날 소환한 덕분에 여기 묶여서
caused by you summoning me is gonna end you right now!
느꼈던 억울함으로 너를 지금 당장 죽여주지!
Jashin-chan Dropkick!
사신짱 드롭킥!
The first episode is also the season finale!
1화가 바로 시즌 최종화가 되는 거지!
Enjoy the rest as highlights!
나머지는 하이라이트로 보시죠!
Damn you, reptile.
못된 파충류야
Damn it! No! No! No!
젠장! 안 돼! 하지 마! 안 돼!
How about some freshly sliced snake?
방금 썬 뱀고기는 어때?
There's plenty.
아주 많아
I'll go buy more meat.
내가 가서 고기 더 사 올게
Too late now.
이젠 너무 늦었어
-Wonder if it's any good? -Yurine Hanazono.
- 맛이 괜찮나 궁금하다 - 하나조노 유리네
Never mess with her.
절대 그녀한테 시비 걸지 마라
Snake meat! It's actually pretty good!
뱀고기! 이거 아주 맛있네!
-What's the password? -Huh?
- 암호는? - 응?
-Um... -Rhymes with Hannibal...
- 그게... - 한니발에 운을 맞춰
Cannibal.
카니발
You may enter!
입장 허가!
Don't scare me! Jashin-chan, you're too paranoid.
놀랐잖아 사신짱, 넌 피해망상에 걸렸어
Never underestimate the human world.
인간 세계를 절대 우습게 보면 안 돼
Jashin-chan, I've been thinking these days...
사신짱, 내가 요즘 생각해 봤는데...
What about?
뭔데?
-This.... -No way!
- 이거... - 설마!
You really got it for me!
날 위해서 사 왔구나!
Huh?
어?
Jashin-chan.
사신짱
-You're up to no good, right? -Yup.
- 너 나쁜 짓 할 거지? - 응
Idiot. What the hell do you think this is?
바보, 넌 이게 뭐라고 생각하는 거야?
You can't have it!
그걸 가지면 안 돼!
-I saw the news. -The criminal escaped.
- 뉴스에서 봤어 - 범인이 탈주했습니다
According to police investigation,
경찰 수사에 따르면
the weapon used...
범행 무기는...
The weapon...
그 무기는...
Surprise, surprise!
놀랐지?
This weapon often gets featured in crime reports.
이 무기는 범죄 보고서에 자주 등장하는 거지
A crowbar!
쇠지레다!
I figured it out.
내가 알아냈어
As I slept and ate all day,
온종일 자고 먹고
woke up and watched TV all day,
일어나서 계속 TV를 보면서
I noticed how the crowbar
쇠지레가 거의 매일
would get featured on TV almost daily!
TV에 나오는 걸 알아챘지
That's right! It's because it's the best weapon to use to kill a human!
맞았어! 이게 바로 인간을 죽이는 최고의 무기다!
Yurine's dead meat!
유리네, 넌 죽었어!
Stop Jashin-chan!
하지 마, 사신짱!
You'll end up killing Yurine!
그러다 결국 유리네를 죽이게 될 거야
-Uh, that's the point. -What?
- 죽이려는 거다 - 뭐?
I'm gonna kill her with one strike!
그 애를 일격에 죽일 거야
Ouch! Stop! Forgive me, please!
아야! 멈춰! 제발 용서해 줘!
No way! I'll never forgive you!
안 돼! 절대 용서 못 해!
ONE STRIKE...?
'일격...?'
Her brains will splatter all over the place!
그 애 뇌가 터져서 사방에 흩어지겠지
This is too good.
너무 좋다
Plus, the crowbar was purchased by Medusa.
게다가 쇠지레는 메두사가 샀어
I'll be innocent, and didn't pay a penny for it.
난 무죄야 한 푼도 안 썼거든
It's the perfect crime!
이건 완전범죄지!
You're like the devil, Jashin-chan!
넌 악마 같아, 사신짱!
Last I checked, I am the devil!
저번에 확인했더니 난 악마더라!
Dear God, please give her divine punishment.
신이시여, 저 애에게 제발 천벌을 내리소서
Nice try, but you're a devil too!
잘하는 짓이다 너도 악마야!
I'm back.
나 왔어
Welcome home!
어서 와!
W-Welcome back.
잘 왔어
Oh, hey, Medusa. How are you?
안녕, 메두사 잘 있었어?
Doing well, thanks.
응, 고마워
That movie you wanted to watch?
네가 보고 싶다던 영화 있지?
Medusa bought it for us!
메두사가 우리 보라고 사 왔다
You must be tired. Why don't you go wind down?
피곤하지? 들어가서 쉬어
Really? Thanks so much, Medusa.
정말? 고마워, 메두사
N-No problem.
아니, 별거 아니야
-Here you go. -Thanks.
- 자, 받아 - 응
Could I go watch it?
가서 봐도 돼?
Of course! Please do.
물론이지, 봐
Don't mind us.
우린 신경 쓰지 마
Holy shit!
젠장!
Get into it, Yurine.
영화에 빠져라, 유리네
Because when you're completely focused on the movie,
네가 영화에 완전히 몰입하면
I'm gonna bust your brains out!
네 머리를 박살 낼 거다!
This is the end.
이걸로 끝이야
Good bye, Yurine. Viewers, it's your lucky day.
잘 가거라, 유리네 시청자 여러분, 운이 좋군요
You all get to witness human brains
인간의 뇌가 터져서
splatter all over the place!
사방으로 튀는 걸 모두 목격하실 겁니다
-Gotcha. -What?
- 잡았다 - 뭐야?
Bam.
에이
-How did she know? -You said it all out loud.
- 쟤가 어떻게 알았지? - 네가 크게 말했잖아
Long lines, too.
아주 길게
Sound engineer! It's called internal monologue!
음향 기사! 그건 내적 독백이라고!
Let's redo this! Cut! Cut!
이건 다시 해! 컷! 컷!
Who are you talking to?
누구에게 말하는 거야?
It was all Medusa!
다 메두사가 그런 거야!
I resisted but she threatened me to do it!
난 싫다고 했는데 하라고 협박했어
Liar! You're unbelievable.
거짓말쟁이! 너 정말 못 말린다
Medusa, you're the liar here!
메두사, 거짓말쟁이는 너야!
-You're setting me up! -I can't watch this.
- 네가 함정을 팠잖아 - 못 봐 주겠군
Jashin-chan.
사신짱
Need I say more?
말 안 해도 알지?
D-Damn it.
제기랄
Now I gotta resort to this. The ultimate soul-crusher!
이걸 쓸 수밖에 없지 최강 영혼 박살 기술!
Jashin-chan Dropkick!
사신짱 드롭킥이다!
J-J-J-Jashin-chan?
사, 사, 사신짱?
I can't get up.
못 일어나겠어
My spine's totally crushed.
내 척추가 완전히 부서졌어
What the hell is that?
대체 저게 뭐지?
You failed miserably.
넌 비참하게 진 거야
So I'm gonna take this opportunity to treat our viewers
난 이걸 기회 삼아 시청자에게 선물할 작정이다
to the slaughter of a devil, where your insides get exposed
악마를 도살해 내장을 다 보이는 거지
-as you get minced. -No! Yurine, stop!
- 널 다져버릴 거다 - 안 돼! 유리네, 하지 마!
No! No!
안 돼! 하지 마!
-You're just gonna turn a blind eye? -Yup.
- 그냥 못 본 척할 거야? - 응
That day, this room was scarlet red.
그날 이 방은 새빨갛게 물들었다
Was it red from
그 붉은빛은
the sun setting in the skyline?
노을 지는 하늘 때문이었을까?
Or the minced meat of Jashin-chan?
아니면 다져진 사신짱의 몸이었을까?
I don't know!
난 모르겠어!
Jeez, I know I can regenerate myself but don't just stand there.
이런, 내가 재생할 수는 있지만 그래도 그냥 서 있기만 할 거야?
Now.
자
Will Jashin-chan fully recover during the commercial break?
사신짱이 광고 시간 동안 완전히 회복할 수 있을까?
I have no idea!
난 몰라!
The murder weapon used was the chainsaw itself.
살인 흉기는 바로 전기톱입니다
You're still censored.
넌 여전히 모자이크 처리됐어
Don't worry, it'll come off soon.
걱정하지 마 곧 다시 나올 거야
The room's gonna be spotless too.
방도 깨끗해질 거고
You can count on me!
넌 나만 믿어!
Okay.
그래
I'm gonna splurge tonight for dinner so come back soon!
오늘 돈 많이 써서 저녁 만들 거니까 빨리 와!
See ya later!
이따 봐!
Bye.
안녕
The censoring was all fake.
모자이크라는 건 다 거짓말이지
Slurp.
후루룩
Yurine has no idea that I'm fully recovered.
내가 완전히 회복된 걸 유리네는 전혀 모른다
TOMATO JUICE
'토마토 주스'
Today's her birthday.
오늘은 그 애 생일이다
I'm gonna invite everyone for a wild celebration.
모두 초대해서 신나게 축하해 줄 거야
For a surprise party to celebrate Yurine's death!
유리네의 죽음을 축하하는 깜짝 파티지!
Plus, my horoscope says I've got the best luck today!
내 별자리 운세에서 오늘이 최고 행운의 날이라고 했어
SCORPIO
'전갈자리'
I got Medusa to pick up the cake and my lucky item for the day.
메두사에게 케이크와 오늘의 행운 아이템을 사오라고 해야지
LUCKY ITEM: STUN GUN
'행운 아이템: 전기 충격기'
I'm gonna be geared up!
모든 도구를 준비할 거야
Ah, yeah! It's gonna be a piece of cake!
그래! 이건 식은 죽 먹기지!
Break.
'휴식'
As you requested.
네가 부탁한 거야
Thanks a lot!
정말 고맙다!
You're always so generous with your money.
넌 언제나 돈에 너그러워
Don't do it, Jashin-chan. Don't commit any more crimes!
하지 마, 사신짱 더는 죄를 짓지 마!
Jashin-chan, planning on killing Yurine again?
사신짱 또 유리네를 죽이려는 거야?
You're gonna end up paying for it anyway.
결국엔 네가 대가를 치르게 될 거야
Don't be ridiculous. I'm all geared up today.
바보 같은 소리 오늘은 단단히 준비했어
-See? -Huh?
- 보여? - 응?
And for the record,
확실히 말하면
I haven't committed any kind of crime so far.
난 아직 죄를 저지른 적이 없어
Since it's been a consistent failure.
계속 실패했으니까
Anyway, let me give you the rundown of how this is gonna go down.
어찌 됐든, 어떻게 할 건지 내가 설명해 줄게
-I'm back. -First, clueless Yurine comes home.
- 나 왔어 - 아무것도 모르는 유리네가 먼저 집에 오지
-Happy Birthday! -We distract her with a surprise.
- 생일 축하해! - 우리가 놀라게 하면 정신없을 거야
Forgive me, God, I know I'm an angel, and yet--
신이시여, 절 용서하소서 제가 천사인 걸 알지만...
Hey! I'm not done here!
어이! 내 말이 안 끝났잖아!
We'll distract her.
우리가 그 애를 정신없게 만들고
Then, I come running up with a present--
그때 내가 달려가서 선물을...
Not! It's the stun gun Medusa picked up for me. Ta-da!
아니! 그건 메두사가 날 위해 사온 전기 충격기야, 짜잔!
I electrocute her.
그 애를 감전시킨다
And she's paralyzed.
그러면 몸을 못 움직이지
Then, I'll finish her using the kitchen knife...
그때 난 부엌칼로 그 애를 없애버릴 거야
By stabbing her in the gut!
칼로 배를 찔러서
The perfect plan.
이 계획은 완벽해
-What a joke. -You'll fail again.
- 말도 안 돼 - 넌 또 실패할 거야
No, I won't! My horoscope said so!
아니, 실패 안 해! 내 운세에 쓰여 있어
-I'm geared up with my lucky item! -I see.
- 행운 아이템도 준비했고! - 그렇구나
Yurine... But why...?
유리네... 하지만 왜...?
You told me to come back soon.
네가 나더러 일찍 오라고 했잖아
Whoopsie.
이런
Not much of a surprise now, huh?
이젠 놀라지 않겠네?
I'm so sorry. I haven't even started cooking yet.
미안해, 난 아직 요리를 시작도 안 했어
-Medusa threatened me to do this! -What?
- 메두사가 다 시킨 거야! - 뭐?
Such a manipulator.
넌 항상 이용만 해
Just give up and apologize.
그냥 포기하고 사과해라
It's a bit too late for that.
그러기엔 너무 늦었다
Take this, Yurine!
받아라, 유리네!
This is your birthday present from me!
너에게 주는 생일선물이다!
Die!
죽어!
What?
뭐야?
What the hell? An electric shaver for beards?
이게 뭐지? 수염 깎는 전기면도기?
What are you trying to tell me?
나한테 왜 이런 거야?
Medusa! You traitor!
메두사! 넌 배신자야!
I just wanted you to stop...
난 그냥 널 막으려고...
Cut the crap!
집어치워!
You better do the same, or else...
너야말로 안 그러면...
U-Um... Is that...a stun gun?
음... 그거 전기 충격기야?
You're a bit slow to notice.
넌 눈치가 없어
But my birthday's October 31st.
내 생일은 10월 31일이다
I'm a Scorpio, just like you.
너처럼 나도 전갈자리야
SCORPIO OCTOBER 23RD-NOVEMBER 21ST
'전갈자리 10월 23일~11월 21일생'
All right! Time to finish decorating!
좋아! 이제 장식하던 거 끝내자!
-Yup. -I'll prepare dinner.
- 응 - 난 저녁 준비할게
Jashin-chan... Come on.
사신짱... 이리 와
Need I say more?
말 안 해도 알지?
No.
응
Yurine!
유리네!
Happy Birthday!
생일 축하해!
Thank you all.
모두 다 고마워
Here's your egg, Yurine.
여기 네 달걀이야, 유리네
-Thanks. -Let me serve the meat for you.
- 고마워 - 고기는 내가 덜어줄게
Delicious. I love the seasoning.
맛있다 이 양념이 너무 맛있어
Actually, that's all Jashin-chan.
사실은 그거 사신짱이 전부 한 거야
Really?
정말?
Hey, is she gonna be okay?
있지, 쟤 괜찮을까?
Oh, she'll be fine. She can regenerate.
응, 괜찮아 재생할 수 있어
-But... -Don't worry, she'll regenerate.
- 하지만... - 걱정하지 마, 재생할 거야
Hey, Medusa. Help me.
어이, 메두사 도와줘
No way!
안 돼!
-Help me. -No way!
- 도와줘 - 싫어!
-Minos... -Never!
- 미노스... - 절대 안 돼!
Jashin-chan.
사신짱
Do you repent?
반성하니?
-Are you sure? -Yes!
- 진짜야? - 응!
Positive?
확실해?
Yes!
응!
Fine, then.
좋아, 그럼
I'll forgive you.
널 용서할게
Dig in, Jashin-chan.
사신짱도 먹어
I still can't move.
난 아직 못 움직여
I'll feed you.
내가 먹여줄게
Medusa prepared such a great meal for us.
메두사가 아주 멋진 식사를 준비했어
Eat the beef tallow.
소기름이나 먹어
So this is what they call, "the Sabbath."
"악마의 연회"가 이런 거구나
Are we all ready?
다들 준비했어?
Come on. Give us a smile.
그러지 말고 웃어
I've had enough today.
오늘은 할 만큼 했다
I had a pretty good time.
난 정말 즐거웠어
You better say that.
넌 그렇겠지
I've sacrificed myself--
날 희생해서...
Now, smile at the camera.
이제 카메라 보고 웃어
-Ready? -If Yurine's a Scorpio like me...
- 준비됐지? - 유리네가 나와 같은 전갈자리면...
Happy Birthday!
생일 축하해!
What about my birthday party?
내 생일 파티는 어떻게 하느냐고!
Dropkick on her! Yeah her! I’ll take you down again!
드롭킥을 날린다! 저 애야! 널 다시 무찌를 거다!
Hate you! Love doesn’t exist in this world
네가 싫어! 이 세상에 사랑이란 없어
Fear the dropkick! An Angel looks for her halo
드롭킥을 겁내라! 천사는 후광을 찾는다
As she starves to death!
굶어 죽어가면서 말이야
It’s a love and hate relationship,
이건 애증 관계야
can’t leave each other alone
서로를 가만히 두지 않지
Like a galaxy-bursting shooting star!
은하에서 터지는 유성처럼
Slowly, slowly, sneak up and DIE!
천천히, 살금살금 몰래 다가가서 죽인다!
Test my heart, don’t stop
내 마음을 떠봐 멈추지 말고
Let’s go! Dream on! No matter human, angel or devil
가자! 꿈꿔! 인간이건 천사건 악마건
We’re a happy family La la la
우리는 행복한 가족이다 랄랄라
Let me say, I love you!!
내가 말할게 난 널 사랑해!
When all is said and done
모든 것이 끝나면
I’m home! Welcome back, it’s hot pot tonight!
나 왔어! 어서 와, 오늘 밤은 스키야키다!
Come, gather everyone! Let’s enjoy this meal!
모두 어서 모여! 이 요리를 즐기자!
For another crazy tomorrow
내일은 또 정신없을 거야
What next? What next? In the end, Wakeup!
뭔데? 또 뭐지? 결국 깨어나!
When the summer heat is making you melt,
여름 열기가 너를 녹일 때
you hear a knock at the door.
문 두드리는 소리가 들린다
There is a brutal snow woman who came from hell that makes even our blood cold.
지옥에서 온 잔인한 스노우먼이 우리의 피도 차갑게 한다
Dropkick on My Devil! Be prepared to be clotheslined by the next episode too!
사신짱 드롭킥! 다음 화에도 공격당할 준비 하세요!